

Chanda Chewe

Full Stack Developer

About Me

Hello! I'm Chanda Chewe. I am passionate about Web Design and Development. I am a skilled **full-stack developer** and am specialised in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Angularjs, Ajax,PHP and PHP Laravel. I am a quick learner and a team worker that gets the job done.

I can easily capitalize on low hanging fruits and quickly maximize timely deliverables for real-time schemas.

Bio

⊞ Wanna Talk?



CLICK ME



chewec03@gmail.com

Github

www.github.com/chandachewe10

- Phone
- +26 0961264154
- +26 0973750029
- **Q** Personal Website

https://www.chandachewe.com

Professional Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

PHP Laravel

PHP

jQuery

Angularjs



Bootstrap

Work Experience

Full-Stack Developer at Esvic Solutions

2021 - present

Responsible for the coding, design and layout of a website according to a company's specifications. As the role takes into consideration user experience and function, a certain level of both graphic design and computer programming is necessary. Once a website has been created, a senior software Web Developer will generally assist with the maintenance and upkeep of the website.

Full-Stack Developer at Freelancer Inc

June, 2021 - September 2021

Using of PHP Laravel framework to make small and large level websites, school management systems and rental management softwares. Implementing the login systems of dynamic websites.

Web Developer at Upwork

2020 (remotely) - June, 2021

My Job here included creating websites using standard HTML/CSS practices, Maintaining and expanding/enhancing the already built website and Developing static and dynamic website, fix errors on existing web pages as per client requirements.



Education

Huawei Certified ICT Associate Security Network Engineer (HCIA-SECURITY) Offered By Huawei

2021

The HCIA-Security curriculum includes: Information security overview, Information Security Standards and Specifications, Common Information Security Threats, Introduction to operating system security, Data Monitoring and Analysis, Digital Forensics, Cybersecurity Emergency Response, Huawei firewall technology, encryption and decryption technology, information security system operation and maintenance, and have the ability to assist in the design of small and medium-sized enterprise security network architecture and deployment and maintenance of the corresponding solutions by protecting the machine from attackers/hackers.

 Bachelor of Science in Physics (Best Graduating Student) from The Copperbelt University

2016 - 2020

Programming experience in C++.

Secondary School from Chimwemwe Secondary School

2012 - 2014

Grade Twelve Certificate

Junior Secondary from Natwange Primary Scool

2003 - 2011

Junior Secondary School Certificate

Portfolio



Frontend / HTML / CSS / JavaScript and PHP Backend

Parexcellence Tutorials Website

Built highly performant website front end for education purposes. Delivered codebase in HTML, CSS and modern JavaScript. Check it out here





Laravel FrameWork / jQuery / JavaScript

Pearchec Website

Web design and Development involving a school management system where students can register and make accounts online. A confirmation link will be sent upon registration to thier respective emails. Only registered students those who have paid in full can access the school resources such as books, papers and tutorial videos others will be denied access by the system. Check it out here





Ajax / PHP / HTML / CSS / JavaScript

Propellantsupport Website

Built highly performant website for an NGO start up organisation. Worked with Ajax jquery and PHP in backend to insert and retrieve comments from the database.

Check it out here





Laravel Breeze FrameWork / jQuery / JavaScript

Online Resume Maker

A simple online resume maker where someone can make a resume in minutes even with mobile phone and download the contents. It is easily done you just have to fill in the blanks and Boom!!! its done. Check it out here

©2021. Some rights reserved. chanda chewe

